What he wants! Your fate was sealed the moment you set foot on a ship!
This time, I'll settle things once and for all,
and you'll have no choice but to admit
that the Foxy Pirates are the strongest in the world!
The guy who's closest to invincible and the most dangerous man!
Boss!
Portia!
Panther!
The straw has bit the dust.
That was lovely, boss, but what's next?
What do you think? We're going to humiliate them!
The same way they humiliated us in that last Daveyberg fight!
All right, you two, let's begin Operation D!
Yay!
Do you hear that? Sounds like a party.
I wonder what everyone's doing over there.
Why don't you go pay them the visit and find out?
I should be fine watching the ship on my own.
Uh, if something bad happened,
I wouldn't want you to get left here by yourself.
Besides, I'd rather stick around and study.
Why you gotta be so tricky all the time, split-head?
If you want to fight, then come and get it!
Ah!
Calm down, Luffy. It'll be okay.
That afro might make you strong,
but right now I think it's making you crazy.
Yep, figures.
All that afro power has gotta go somewhere.
Please tell me that's supposed to be a joke.
Getting revenge is one thing,
but using us to take out his enemies is pretty low.
So what if you had to beat up a couple of losers?
I'm more worried about our goals.
Any way you look at it, he bit off more than he can chew.
He should know better than to get on our bad side.
We'll tear this sorry ship to pieces in no time flat.
You can't beat the five of us.
Or the four of you, at least.
Well, anyway, before we can wreak any havoc,
we have to find a way out of here.
And since this is Foxy's ship,
I'm sure there's some dirty trick involved.
I think we can just break through the wall.
What the hell is this place?
Chubby, Chubby, wherever could you be?
Are you hiding from me again?
Geez, if you don't come out, I'll have to punish you.
Is something the matter, Doctor?
Uh, no, it's nothing.
Why you, this is the lamest trick you could possibly pull!
Let me handle this!
Luffy!
Listen, I'm on to you!
Tell me where you're hiding, Split Head, now!
I don't know what you're talking about!
I wonder where he could be?
Even for Luffy, this is pretty bad.
Should we say something?
This is kind of awkward.
Let's just see how this plays out.
Well, it looks like Split Head's not here, guys!
Behind you!
Luffy, take a closer look at that face.
Okay, but it looks pretty normal to me.
You're not Portia!
You're Split Head's sister, aren't you?
Ah, this is getting me nowhere!
Ah!
It was Split Head all along!
I'm gonna make you pay for tricking me!
I don't know if I should laugh or cry about this.
Say a prayer, Strahat!
Slow, slow, boom!
Ah!
Haven't you fools learned your lesson?
Sure you can run,
but my slow, slow beam will always find you!
I've had about enough of that thing.
Yeah, no kidding!
Slow, slow beam!
Ah, look out!
Ah!
Keep your hands off her!
Watch where you're going!
Ah!
Sanjay!
Zoro!
They got hit!
I should have known you dodged, Strahat!
You coward!
Hey!
Stop running away!
Come on, just fight us already!
Hey, Nami, let's go!
I'll see you guys when your 30 seconds are up, okay?
No!
Don't leave us like this!
Nami!
Come back!
Wait!
What's that?
There's some kind of note on the door!
Let's see.
Come on!
It's a man's path!
No women allowed!
So, any clue what that's all about?
Nope!
Beats me!
But we better stay on our toes!
No!
Is something the matter, Doctor?
No, it's nothing.
That was about to get ugly.
For once, I agree with you.
Looks like a regular old hallway to me.
Yeah.
I take it back!
This is weird!
What kind of place is this?
Oh, I see.
It's like a holding cell under there.
These guys probably did something bad and got locked away as punishment.
They can leer all they want.
I'm going ahead!
Wait!
It's a woman!
All right!
It's been so long!
Ugh!
I can't do it.
I can't give those creeps the satisfaction.
Leave it to me, Nami.
Huh?
What are you...?
Seems like they've been locked up in the dark for a while now.
And if that's the case, they must be weak to light.
All I gotta do is bust out one of my flashballs and they'll be blind as bats in no time.
And then we'll make a break for it, huh?
Right.
Now close your eyes, cause here it comes!
Okay, let's go!
You've got it!
Help me!
I got her!
Musak, no!
My manhood!
Let me touch her too!
Don't worry!
I'll never forget your noble sacrifice!
Don't leave me!
It's been too long!
She's so soft!
Is something the matter, Doctor?
No, it's nothing.
That was a close one.
Huh?
Another weird room.
Hey, Nami!
Luffy?
Took you long enough.
What are you doing sitting down in the middle of Foxy's ship?
What am I doing?
I'm eating these rice crackers and having some tea!
Well, duh!
I can tell that much!
You've done well to make it this far!
Congratulations!
But now that you're both here, perhaps I should be congratulating myself instead.
You see, it was my plan to separate you two from the rest of the crew all along!
Luffy I get, but why me?
Because you're obviously the brains of the operation!
With you and the captain out of the picture, the Straw Hats are as good as done for!
I bet those other goons will wipe themselves out long before I get to them!
Hmm, that's a good plan.
This could be bad.
But hey, for now, might as well fight!
Fee-fee-fee-fee!
Right on, brother!
That's what I'd like you to hear!
Oh, yay!
Does this mean we'll finally get our revenge on Straw Hat?
What are those things?
Never seen that one before.
But this one is called Gorilla Pants.
Puncher!
Not pants, it's Gorilla Puncher 13!
Now, get ready!
Here comes the Gorilla Punch!
Leave this one to me, Nami!
Right now!
Gum-gum!
I wouldn't do that if I were you, Rubber Boy!
Remember what happens when you touch the globe?
Stop!
It burns!
You forgot! It is you!
Luffy!
You better not ignore me!
Cause if you do, Mr. Donkey Kicker 18 is gonna stop you, silly!
Hey, Nami!
Huh?
Water, water, water, water, water, water, water, water!
Oh, I see.
That's a good idea!
Wow!
I knew you were pathetic,
but if you think you can beat us with magic tricks,
you're just plain crazy!
All right.
Here goes!
Today's forecast is rain!
Thunderstorm?
Tempo!
Nice try!
But it's gonna take more than a little clappy weather to bring down my Gorilla Punch!
Ah!
You really are stupid, aren't you?
If this thing can take punches at lightning, you think a little rain can make any difference?
We won't know until we try, right?
All right, have it your way!
Since you clearly don't have any common sense, I'll have to beat some into you!
Gorilla Punch Golden Hips!
Can't burn me now!
Somebody stop him, quick!
Hmm.
...
Aah!
Wh kicked!
Ha!
Ha-ha. Now come, go!
Ah! Let me go!
Hey, boss, you're not gonna hit us, right?
Holy smoke!
No!
What was that?
Look, it's boss!
Did he beat the Straw Hats?
Men, I've returned!
Yeah!
I got beat!
See? Just like I said, you took too long and they finished the fight without us.
The only reason we're late is because you got lost!
Say, Rubber Boy, I lost fair and square to a fellow pirate so you won't hear me complain. Scan me, turn me in or do whatever you want!
All right, then. In that case, why don't you let them join your crew again?
What? But they stole the Sexy Foxy and stabbed me in the back!
Yeah, so?
I said I wouldn't complain, so have it your way.
All right, men! Straw Hat says you get a free pass, so that's how it's gonna be!
Boss? You mean it?
Go ahead! Talk to them!
Thank you, Straw Hat!
Listen up, frogs! If you wanna be foxes again, then that's fine with me!
Ooh! Ooh!
Yeah!
Well, he's got charisma, if nothing else.
We love you, boss!
Kinda makes me mad!
Boss!
You better not be switching sides on me!
I was just kidding, my darling!
Mother Boy, I just did a head to take care!
You too, Splithead!
So funky!
Yeah!
Oh, no you don't!
Good. I thought you'd never wake up.
Where am I? Last I remember, I was...
Hey! You left me stranded with those creeps!
That's not what happens at all. Did you forget?
Oh, when you put it that way, then it all makes sense.
I don't remember beating up all those guys, but I guess I am pretty strong, huh?
Hey, boss, now that we have our old crew back, we're finally done dealing with those horrible straw hat pirates, right?
Not a chance.
Didn't take long for boss to cook up another scheme.
No matter what it takes, we have to cross the straw hats.
Otherwise, we're going to be stuck with this stupid-looking flag for the rest of our lives.
That being said, I think you know our destination.
Yeah!
I'm coming for your upper boy.
Hey, guys! I think I see an island!
Hmm.
Looks uninhabited to me.
Ready, the anchor! Let's go check it out!
Find me some ingredients and I'll start cooking lunch.
All right!
Listen, nothing slimy or gross, okay?
What does it matter? Once it's in your stomach, it's all the same.
Get over yourself.
Ow!
Hey, Sanji!
Hey! We got fish, fruit, and everything! It was easy!
Nice work!
Cheers!
Yummy!
It tastes a lot better if you didn't scarf it down.
I figured you wouldn't have any room left for dinner since you finished off all the snacks on the ship.
I'm just getting warmed up!
That's not good since we've decimated half our supplies already.
Robin, you better eat fast before all the food is gone.
Just let me get to a stopping point first.
Okay, but I heard that if you read too much, you'd turn into a yucky buck.
They call them bookworms.
I found you, Straw Hat.
You kids ready to teach him a lesson?
You bet we are.
Let's go!
Anytime, boss.
One, two, one, two, one.
Hey, boss, they're all looking right this way.
What's the big deal?
Even if they do notice us, they'll think we're just an ordinary crab.
I hope they don't try to eat us.
Is that who I think it is?
Who else would be that stupid?
Don't these guys have anything better to do?
Okay, while they're eating, let's wreck their ship.
What's going on back there?
I caught a crab! Let's eat it!
He's kidding, right?
Nope, and I think he's about to get a nasty surprise.
Stop! We're not food, you fool!
Hey, come back! You look yummy!
Oh, yeah? Then take a bite of this!
Now's our chance! Crab Crab Punch!
The only thing you'll be tasting is the food.
Hey, now! You better learn your place if you know what's good for you, crab.
Now open up!
Because I'm going to eat you!
Wow! I can't believe you guys got eaten by that big crab.
That's pretty lame.
Get that out of your mouth!
Now that that's taken care of, let's get back to our barbecue.
All that crab assing worked out my appetite.
Hey, that isn't done cooking yet.
Whatever. Still tastes good to me.
Come on, boss. I want barbecue, too.
Not too bad!
We didn't come here to eat. We came here to fight.
But don't worry, because soon we'll taste very...
Thank you for waiting, mademoiselle.
I hope that my barbecue special is to your liking.
Oh, you bet!
Here you go. Help yourself.
Oh! This is positively scrumptious!
Why don't you come to Boss's ship and be our cook?
Oh, no! Don't tempt me!
If you ask, I might have to say yes!
Please, by all means, don't let me stop you.
Hello? This is the communications room.
Hi, it's me.
Boss has knocked out, so we're done here.
Come and get us, okay?
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm. Don't worry.
Yeah, he'll be fine.
All right, then. See you in a sec.
Bye-bye, Mr. Cook!
I'll never forget your yummy barbecue!
It touched my heart!
Take care, Portia! I'll miss you!
Are you sure you don't want to go back with her?
No way.
You may not appreciate good food,
but Nami and Robin deserve nothing less than the best.
Right, Nami?
Come on, guys! Let's go!
We still need to stock up on some emergency supplies!
Wait for me, Nami-Swan!
Hey, Chopper, did you find any new herbs to use?
Mm-hmm. This place has all sorts of neat stuff.
I got a good stock, but I'm still looking in case I miss something.
Which reminds me, I noticed something weird a second ago.
There's a little groove along the trail here.
I wonder what it is.
Oh, you're right. That is weird.
Looks like a bicycle or something came through here.
Come on, that doesn't make any sense.
There's nobody else on the island.
Why would there be a bicycle?
Yeah, that's a good point.
Hey, check it out!
We're almost through the jungle!
Well, that's a letdown.
Just looks like a whole lot of nothing out here.
He's excited. Did I miss something?
I don't get it either.
Maybe he found some new herbs.
Huh?
Chopper, you cheater!
You were going to hog that big mushroom all to yourself, weren't you?
Get back here!
Hey! What happened? Are you okay?
There must be something behind that rock.
Come on, hurry!
Whoa! You're not a mushroom!
Hmm? A raccoon dog.
Can't you see the antlers? I'm a reindeer!
I saw you fall! Are you hurt?
Who the heck is that?
What's going on?
I don't know. Someone's here.
Do you mind? I was sleeping.
Did you hit my friend?
Oh, man! That guy is huge!
I thought we were alone on this island!
You know him?
Hey, is this guy an enemy?
Who is he?
If Robin's freaking out, then so am I!
Something's wrong.
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Hold on.
Look, I know you're surprised to see me, but don't get so worked up.
It's not like I came here on official orders or anything.
It's a nice day, so I decided to go for a ride.
Orders, huh? And who is it you work for?
He's a marine.
Not only that, he's known as one of the world government's ultimate powerhouses.
What, for real?
I'm afraid so.
This is Admiral Aokiji from Navy Headquarters.
My, my, you've grown into quite the lovely lady, haven't you?
Nico Robin?
My, my, my
Yes!
It's a real one for us.
To be gone
Next, One Piece, Navy Headquarters Admiral Aokiji,
the ferocity of an ultimate powerhouse.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!